I am a massive science fiction geek.
我是一个超级科幻迷。
Ever since I was young, I‘ve been captivated by tales of interstellar adventure, aliens, robots, and cutting-edge technology.
从我小时候起，我就被星际冒险、外星人、机器人以及前沿的科技故事所迷住。
I always loved the concept of cyborgs.
我一直很喜欢半机械人的概念。
That’s a human-robot hybrid.
那是一种人类与机器人的混合体。
They are ordinary humans who have been enhanced in some way by technology; more intelligence, faster speed or better resilience to disease and damage.
他们是普通人类，但通过技术在某些方面得到了增强，比如拥有更高的智力、更快的速度，或者对疾病和伤害有更强的恢复能力。
Great ideas, but I never thought I‘d see them in my lifetime.
这些想法很棒，但我从未想过在我的有生之年能看到它们成为现实。
Well, I stand corrected.
好吧，我错了。
Integrated biology and technology is already here and people have wasted no time utilising it to re-engineer their bodies.
生物与科技的融合已经成为现实，人们毫不犹豫地利用它来改造自己的身体。
Take, for example, Neil Harbisson, who has an antenna protruding from his head that allows him to hear colour, or Moon Ribas, who has an implant that allows her to sense seismic activity.
例如，尼尔·哈比森，他的头上伸出一个天线，这使他能够“听”到颜色；还有穆恩·里巴斯，她植入了一个装置，能够感知地震活动。
Now, neither are abilities that I particularly covet, but it’s a start.
当然，这两种能力都不是我特别渴望拥有的，但这只是一个开始。
And it doesn‘t end there.
而且这还不止于此。
As technology increases so too will our ability to enhance ourselves through it.
随着科技的发展，我们通过科技来增强自身的能力也会不断提高。
One of the latest developments is the graphene tattoo.
最新的进展之一就是石墨烯“纹身”。
Not an actual tattoo at all, but more like a patch, the graphene tattoo could revolutionise biomedical monitoring.
它根本不是真正的纹身，而更像是一个贴片，这种石墨烯“纹身”可能会彻底改变生物医学监测。
It looks much like a transparent plaster, but with a gold coloured circuit board contained within it.
它看起来很像一块透明的创可贴，但里面有一个金色的电路板。
This circuit is the graphene.
这个电路就是石墨烯。
Graphene is a form of carbon, but it’s 200 times stronger than steel and conducts electricity better than gold, which is the component typically used in electronics.
石墨烯是碳的一种形态，但它比钢强200倍，并且比通常用于电子设备的黄金导电性能更好。
The human body is basically an electrical machine.
人体基本上是一部电器。
When in contact with the skin, the graphene in the plaster is able to read and conduct the electricity — allowing it to easily be used as a medical monitor for heart-rate and pulse, among other things.
当创可贴中的石墨烯与皮肤接触时，它能够读取和传导电流——这使得它可以很容易地被用作心率和脉搏等生理指标的医学监测设备，除此之外还有许多其他功能。
And even more, graphene tattoos can be used as bioelectronic controllers, as demonstrated by one engineer who attached them to his eyelids in order to direct which way a drone flew, just by looking with his eyes!
甚至更厉害的是，石墨烯“纹身”还可以用作生物电子控制器，就像一位工程师所展示的那样，他把石墨烯“纹身”贴在眼皮上，以便仅仅通过眼睛看就能控制无人机的飞行方向！
I know that biotechnology is a long way from allowing humans to be able to lift a car or run halfway around the world in a single day, like I wanted to be able to do when I was a child.
我知道生物技术距离让人类能够像我小时候希望的那样，举起一辆汽车或者在一天内绕地球半圈，还有很长的路要走。
But, it‘s improving all the time and once the price of graphene falls, who knows what else we’ll be able to do?
它一直在不断进步，而且一旦石墨烯的价格下降，谁知道我们还能做到什么呢？
I‘ll see you in the future!
未来见！